(Raj:)Well, maybe there's a way
to appear nonaggressive,
(Raj:)but also be able to protect
ourselves if necessary.
(Raj:)Like smiling and waving
with one hand,
(Raj:)but the other hand holding
the severed head of a tiger.
(Howard:)You want to send
a passive-aggressive message
(Howard:)out into the universe?
(Howard:)That's ridiculous.
(Raj:)Oh, you mean passive-aggressive
(Raj:)like posting pictures
of you and your wife
(Raj:)eating cosmopolitan balls
(Raj:)that you know belong
in my mouth?
(Sheldon:)Perhaps Howard meant
passive-aggressive
(Sheldon:)like asking our group
to help on your project,
(Sheldon:)and then only
choosing Leonard.
(sighs) Look, I'm sorry
I hurt your feelings,
(Raj:)but you do have
strong personalities
(Raj:)and always end up taking over.
(Howard:)It's not always.
(Leonard:)What about when we went
to Comic-Con
(Leonard:)and dressed like Jabba the Hutt?
(Leonard:)You got to be Jabba's head,
and I got to be
(Leonard:)his fat slug butt.
(Sheldon:)We looked great.
(Leonard:)You let a guy sit on me.
(Howard:)He was dressed as Princess Leia.
(Howard:)It made a nice picture.